Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive
1960-2010
1973-2000
Fales Library and Special Collections
Lotringer, Sylvère
MSS.221
106.5 Linear Feet in 175 boxes, 2 flat-file folders, 14 film reel cans, 1 roll storage container, and a number of items within 11 shared boxes.
Sylvère Lotringer is a literary critic, cultural theorist, filmmaker, and founder of the journal and independent press Semiotext(e). The Sylvère Lotringer Papers contain correspondence, manuscripts, clippings, and financial records associated with Semiotext(e) and Lotringer's work as a literary critic and cultural theorist. They also contain audiovisual recordings related to his films and books, as well as recordings of lectures, events, and press appearances.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was purchased by NYU Libraries from Sylvère Lotringer in 2008. An accretion of 4 boxes was added in October 2015. In April 2018 Lotringer donated an additional nine audiocassettes of Kathy Acker interviews; the accession number associated with this gift is 2018.059. Lotringer donated an additional box of correspondence and ephemera in July 2018; the accession number with this gift is 2018.117.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 13 series, with oversize material and an archived website arranged separately at the end of the inventory:
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Semiotext(e) Projects
Series III: Manuscripts from the Semiotext(e) Archive
Series IV: Subject Files
Series V: Sylvère Lotringer Projects
Series VI: Photographic Materials
Series VII: Financial Papers
Series VIII: Clippings and Photocopies
Series IX: Editions of Publications
Series X: Video
Series XI: Audio
Series XII: Film
Series XIII: Computer Disks
OVERSIZE Series I: Correspondence
OVERSIZE Series II: Semiotext(e) Projects
OVERSIZE Series III: Manuscripts
OVERSIZE Series IV: Subject Files
OVERSIZE Series V: Sylvère Lotringer Projects
OVERSIZE Series VI: Photographic Materials
OVERSIZE Series VIII: Clippings and Photocopies
OVERSIZE Series IX: Copies of Publications
Archived website
Biographical Note
Sylvère Lotringer is a literary critic, cultural theorist, and filmmaker. He is best known for founding the journal Semiotext(e), which is largely credited with introducing the work of French theorists like Jean Baudrillard, Gilles Deleuze, Paul Virilio, Félix Guattari, Michel Foucault and Jean-François Lyotard to an English-speaking audience.
Lotringer was born in Paris to Polish-Jewish immigrants. He spent the Nazi occupation of Paris as a "hidden child", later relocating with his family to Israel. He returned to Paris and studied at the Sorbonne, where he founded the literary magazine L'Étrave. In 1964, Lotringer entered the École pratique des Hautes Études in Paris where he wrote his doctoral dissertation on Virginia Woolf's novels under the supervision of Roland Barthes and Lucien Goldmann. During this period, he organized conferences at the Maison des Lettres of the Sorbonne where he forged connections with French literary critics, sociologists and writers as well as with the Bloomsbury Group in London (Leonard Woolf, T.S. Eliot, Vita Sackville-West, David Garnet, etc.) as a freelance writer for Louis Aragon's journal Les Lettres Françaises.
After teaching in Scotland, Turkey, Australia and the American Midwest, Lotringer joined the French and Comparative Literature Faculty at Columbia University in 1972, where he eventually became Professor Emeritus. In 1973, Lotringer founded the journal Semiotext(e) with a group of Columbia University graduate students. After three scholarly, bilingual issues on semiotics, Lotringer and his group organized the "Schizo-Culture" conference in 1975 at Columbia University, which featured Félix Guattari, Michel Foucault, Gilles Deleuze, Jean-François Lyotard, Ronald D. Laing, Ti-Grace Atkinson, John Cage, and William S. Burroughs. In 1978, Lotringer staged "The Nova Convention," a large downtown New York event that gathered members of the American Counter Culture (from Patti Smith and Timothy Leary to Franz Zappa, Laurie Anderson and Allen Ginsberg) as an homage to William S. Burroughs.
Subsequent issues of Semiotext(e) moved away from the original scholarly format, enlisting a crew of artists and featuring experimental typographics, controversial topics and an ever-expanding cast of French theorists. In 1983, Lotringer founded Semiotext(e) emph>'s "Foreign Agents" series to present their work in a portable book format stripped of the usual academic introductions and afterwords. In 1990, as "French Theory" became established in America, Chris Kraus added the "Native Agents" book series -- meant to present home-grown fiction writers as American counterparts to the French theorists -- to Semiotext(e)'s output. Later, Lotringer expanded Semiotext(e)'s roster to include an "Active Agents" series featuring the Black Panthers.
Lotringer directed several films, including The Golden Bowl, or, Repression (1984-1989) and How to Shoot a Crime, which were co-directed with Chris Kraus; Too Sensitive to Touch (1981), co-directed with Michael Oblowitz; and solo works Second Hand Hitler (unfinished, circa 1985), Violent Femmes (1998), and The Man Who Disappeared (2015).
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact NYU Special Collections (special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596) with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact NYU Special Collections (special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596) with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive includes correspondence, manuscripts, clippings, and financial records associated with Lotringer's work as a literary critic and cultural theorist, and as the founder of the journal and independent press Semiotext(e).
The collection also contains audio, video, and film materials related to the films that Lotringer directed -- The Golden Bowl, or, Repression (1984-1989) and How to Shoot a Crime, which were co-directed with Chris Kraus; Too Sensitive to Touch (1981), co-directed with Michael Oblowitz; and solo works Second Hand Hitler (unfinished, circa 1985), Violent Femmes (1998), and The Man Who Disappeared (2015). Audiovisual materials in this collection include various edits of films, source materials, soundtracks, press appearances by Lotringer, footage from Lotringer's film studies, films by his contemporaries, event recordings, and source materials such as interviews that Lotringer used to write his books.
Viewer discretion is advised for materials related to the film How to Shoot a Crime, which includes footage of real events, and the book Overexposed, which may contain descriptions of sexual violence.
Appraisal
In March 2012, three linear feet of material created by Chris Kraus was returned to Kraus at the donor's request, as per the original acquisition agreement. In September 2025, 3 VHS tapes with duplicative content were deaccessioned.
Alternative spaces (Arts facilities); Amateur films -- Production and direction; American fiction -- 20th century.; American fiction -- New York (State) -- New York.; Artists -- New York (N.Y.); Art criticism.; Artists' writings; Correspondence.; Kitchen (New York, N.Y.); Literary editors.; Literature, Experimental.; Literature, Modern -- Translations; Manuscripts for publication.; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Popular culture -- United States.; Postmodernism (Literature); Publishers and publishing -- United States.; Semiotext(e) active agents series.; Semiotext(e) double agents series.; Semiotext(e) foreign agents series.; Semiotext(e) native agents series.; Semiotext(e) intervention series.; Semiotics.; Small presses -- New York (State) -- New York.; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Artaud, Antonin, 1896-1948; Bataille, Georges, 1897-1962; Baudrillard, Jean, 1929-2007; Burroughs, William S., 1914-1997; Deleuze, Gilles, 1925-1995; Foucault, Michel, 1926-1984; Guattari, Félix, 1930-1992; King, Kenneth, 1948-; Kraus, Chris, 1963-; Lyotard, Jean-François, 1924-1998; Myles, Eileen; Nietzsche, Friedrich Wilhelm, 1844-1900; Paris, Jean; Rattray, David; Saussure, Ferdinand de, 1857-1913; Simon, Claude; Smith, Duncan; Virilio, Paul; Wojnarowicz, David
- Series I: Correspondence
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains both Sylvere Lotringer's personal correspondence and the correspondence of the Semiotext(e) group. It has been arranged into five subseries: Correspondence from Individuals, Organizations, and Unknown Senders; as well as a subseries of Flyers and Press Releases and another of Address Books. In subseries A, an organizational affiliation may be indicated in parentheses for some individuals. This is meant to help the researcher but has not been done exhaustively. This series does not contain all the correspondence in the archive. Correspondence that was found foldered with a particular manuscript or project has been retained in its original position.
  - Subseries A: Individuals
    Scope and Content note
    Materials have been arranged alphabetically by name of sender--or recipient in the case of drafts of letters written by Sylvère Lotringer. Because this series contains both Lotringer's personal correspondence and that of Semiotext(e), it includes letters addressed to recipients other than Lotinger, such as Jim Fleming and Chris Kraus. These letters are nevertheless filed under the name of their sender. Where a sender has an important affiliation to a magazine or institution, this information has been noted in parentheses; such information is meant to be helpful but is not exhaustive. Correspondence with organizations and institutions that is business-oriented rather than personal can be found in Subseries B; however, such separations are not entirely firm. Files may include manuscripts, photographs and other material that was included with the letters. Materials in each folder are arranged chronologically, with undated materials at the end.
    - "A", undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abarbanel, Stephanie, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abish, Walter, c. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Acker, Kathy, 1980-91 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Adam, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [Ahahaus, Jean-Jacques], 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alden, Todd, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alexander, George, 1980-3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alice, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Aline, 1957-61 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alkadhi, Rheim Bragdon, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Alland, Sonia, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Allen, Elizabeth Brereton, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Altomare, Carlo, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Altounian, Nicole Rousset, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Amara, Nadia, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Amaral, Antonio, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Anderson, Fortner (Editions Dromos), 1985-7 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Anderson, [Lamis], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Anderson, Lisa, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Andrew, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Annie, 1986-7 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Anton, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Anzalone, Filadelfo, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Apples, Jonathon, 1977-8 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Aragon, Louis, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Arcade, Penny, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Arnoux, Rosemary, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Asada, Akira, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Asaoka, Kayko, 1984-9 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Assad, Maria L., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Assadeck, Mohamed Elmehdy, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - [Auden, Evie], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Ausgang, Anthony, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Auster, Paul, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Ay Abby, Mohamed, 1979-84 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - B, Anita, 1962-3 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - B, Sandra, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Backes, Catherine, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Baehr, Jo-ann, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Baer, Marshall, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Baldessari, John, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Balestrini, Nanni, 1982-4 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Ballard, J.G., 1983-7 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Ballas, Theo, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - [Barkos], Arnold, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Barrie, Lita (FACT Magazine), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Barron, [Stephen], undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Barroso, Donzie, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - [Bartenieff, George], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Barthes, Roland, 1964-75 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Baselitz, Georg, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Baudrillard, Jean, 1981-2007 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Baudry, F., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Baum, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - [Bayar, Jin Leyla], 1969-72 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Bear, Liza, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Beard, Michael, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Beauchard, M.C. (Association Chantiers), 1993-4 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Beck, Johannes (Minus Verlag), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Beck, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Becker, Julie, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Beckley, Constance, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Beckmann, John, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Bedoya, Roberto (Getty Museum), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Behar, Henri, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Behenna, Veralyn, 1991-2 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Beiler, Mervin and Verna, 1988-9 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Beitchman, Phil, c. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Bella, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Bellour, Raymond, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Bender, Gretchen, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - [Benhamon, Yonah], 1958-60 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Bennett, Yvonne, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Benoist, Marie, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Berglund, Greg, 1977-9 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Bergounioux, Frederic, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - [Bergst], Cynthia, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Berkeley, David, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Berman, Tosh, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Bernard, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Bernheim, Kurt, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Bernstein, Charles, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Berry, Jake, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Berthoud, Chris De Coulon, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Bifo, 1991-4 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Binet, M. et Mme (in-laws of SL), 1969-70 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Binion, Sandra, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Bird, Jon, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Bishop, Tom, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Blair, undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Blake, Barbara (City Gallery, Wellington), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Blanchard, David, 1986-93 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Blanchot, Maurice, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Blaushild, Lisa, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Bob, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Boggs, Carl, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Bollande, Jennifer, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Bordowitz, Gregg, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Borradori, Giovanna, c. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Bouchardeau, Huguette (HB Editions), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Boughali, Mohamed, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Bouillon, Victor, 1990-2 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Bouloc, Denys-Paul, 1986-7 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - [Bounk], Bruce, c. 1990 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Bowman, Frank Paul, 1970-4 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Boyne, Ray, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Bradovich, Lea, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Bree, Germaine, undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Breger, Udo, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Breit, Mark, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Brenner, Hildegard, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Brent, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Brian, undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Brinkley, Tony, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - [Brit], 1990 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Brod Miller, Claudine, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Brodsky, Michael, 1991-2 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Brosman, Kate, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Brossard, Olivier (Consulat de France), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Broughton, John M., undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Brown, N. O., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Breuer, Lee, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - Brun, Catherine, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - Bud, undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - [Buenl, Gerard], 1974 (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Burgelin, Claude, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - Burns, Bill, 1997-2007 (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Burroughs, William, 1978-97 (Box 1, Folder 129)
    - Butler, Eugenia, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - [Buzari], Paschutan, 1993-6 (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - Bynum, Thomas, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - Cage, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - Caiafa, Janice, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - Caley, Shaun, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - Callahan, Anne M., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Callard, Andrea, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Camelia, 1992-3 (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - Camille, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - Camus, Albert, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - Canby, Vincent, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 141)
    - Cantrell, Emily, 1985-95 (Box 1, Folder 142)
    - Carlin, John, 1977-80 (Box 1, Folder 143)
    - [Carlo], 1992 (Box 1, Folder 144)
    - Carlos, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 145)
    - [Carol], 1994 (Box 1, Folder 146)
    - Carpenter, Joan, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 147)
    - Cascaito, [Jim], 1984 (Box 1, Folder 148)
    - Cataldo, Susan, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 149)
    - Catherine, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 150)
    - Cavalier, Robert J., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 151)
    - Caws, Peter, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 152)
    - Cermelli, Angelina, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 153)
    - Chambers, Ross, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 154)
    - Chantal, undated (Box 1, Folder 155)
    - [Chardaine, Nicole], 1960-7 (Box 1, Folder 156)
    - Charles, Michel, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 157)
    - Charlesworth, Sarah, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 158)
    - Cheatham, Linda, 1978-84 (Box 1, Folder 159)
    - Cherry, Regina, 1997-9 (Box 1, Folder 160)
    - Chessid, Ilona, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 161)
    - Chien, Wendy, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 162)
    - Chin, Daryl, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 163)
    - Cholodenko, Alan, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 164)
    - [Christian and Suiri], undated (Box 1, Folder 165)
    - Christo, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 166)
    - Christopher, undated (Box 1, Folder 167)
    - Christus 777 (Purge Magazine), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 168)
    - [Chuilles, Genevieve], 1963 (Box 1, Folder 169)
    - Clark, Charles Lynn, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 170)
    - Clark, Michael, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 171)
    - Clark, Priscilla P., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 172)
    - [Claudia], 1978 (Box 1, Folder 173)
    - Clayton, Alan J., 1987-9 (Box 1, Folder 174)
    - Clement, Catherine, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 175)
    - Cobey, Peter, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 176)
    - Cochin, Jacques, undated (Box 1, Folder 177)
    - Cohen, Edith, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 178)
    - Cohen, Sande, 1991-9 (Box 1, Folder 179)
    - [Coleman], Beth, undated (Box 1, Folder 180)
    - Collins, Anthony, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 181)
    - Cooke, Douglas O., 1969-70 (Box 1, Folder 182)
    - Coon, Ralph, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 183)
    - Cooper, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 184)
    - Cooper, Denis, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 185)
    - Corbett, John, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 186)
    - Cornand, Brigitte, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 187)
    - Corpet, Olivier, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Corpier, Leslee, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Corradi, Juan E., 1986 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Corredor, Eva, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Corten, Andre, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Cortez, Diego, 1977-82 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Cote, Philippe, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - [Cotnoir, Brian], 1980 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Cottrell, Pierre, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Coulon, Philippe, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Courtine, Jean-Jacques, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Craig, 1996 (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Crasta, Richard, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Craveiro, Isabel, undated (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Crisp, George R., undated (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - Croissant, Klaus, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Cush, 1996 (Box 129, Folder 25)
    - D, Mrs., 1977 (Box 129, Folder 26)
    - Daitch, Susan, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 27)
    - Daniel, c. 1993 (Box 129, Folder 28)
    - Damisch, Hubert, 1972-4 (Box 129, Folder 29)
    - Danowski, Deborah, 1982-3 (Box 129, Folder 30)
    - Dass, Vasanthi, 1999 (Box 129, Folder 31)
    - Dassas, Veronique, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 32)
    - Davenport, John H., 1986 (Box 129, Folder 33)
    - David, 1974-89 (Box 129, Folder 34)
    - Davidou, Gregor, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 35)
    - Davies, Matt, 1983 (Box 129, Folder 36)
    - Davis, Lydia, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 37)
    - De Certeau, Michel, 1972-87 (Box 129, Folder 38)
    - Decker, Kim, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 39)
    - De Cointet, Guy, 1981-2 (Box 129, Folder 40)
    - [Decoust], Michele, 1982 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Deguy, Michel, 1970 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - De Kerret, Hugues (Ambassade de France), 1981-9 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - De Landa, Manuel, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Delcourt, Xavier Marianne, undated (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Deleuze, Fanny, 2000 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Deleuze, Gilles, 1976-86 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - [Delliela], undated (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Delogu, C. Jon, 1992 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Demougin, Jacques (Larousse), 1973 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Denis, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - [Denise], undated (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - [Denys, Anne], 1986 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Dequeter, Docteur J., 1985 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Derrida, Jacques, 1973-82 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Desrez, Jacqueline, 1996-2000 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Dethier, Jean (Centre Georges Pompidou), 1986 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Devereaux, Kent, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Dewdney, Christopher, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Dewey, Fred, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Diamond, Sara, 1999 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Dickson, Jane, 1996 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Diedre, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - [Digot], Jean, 1983 (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Dinerstein, Jim, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Dixit, Kanak, 1990 (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - Dodie, 1996 (Box 130, Folder 27)
    - Dolan, Frederick and McNeill, Linda, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 28)
    - Dominique, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 29)
    - Domke, Noelle and DiBernardi, Dominic, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 30)
    - Domkowski, Christine, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 31)
    - Donaldson, Weber D., 1977 (Box 130, Folder 32)
    - [Donnard, Giselle], 1982 (Box 130, Folder 33)
    - Dorsey, Laurens M., 1989 (Box 130, Folder 34)
    - Dos Santos, Judite, 1986-9 (Box 130, Folder 35)